[{"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/鸟类动物_2组/Left/飞翔的鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_3.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/5_特殊类别-猫/猫_L1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_7.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/草/草_6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/5_特殊类别-猫/猫_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/树苗.svg", "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/鸟类动物_2组/Left/飞翔的鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最上面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，哪个在最下面。", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-4.svg"], "type": "pos-sequence-select4"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-02"}]